{
  "quiz" : [
    {
      "quizOptions" : [
        {
          "question": "During the First World War, which country signed the Peace Treaty (1917) with Germany?",
          "answer" : "Russia",
          "options": [
            "England",
            "USA",
            "Russia",
            "Austria"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "When did United Kingdom declared war on Germany which lead to World War II?",
          "answer" : "3rd September 1939",
          "options": [
            "4th April 1939",
            "18th August 1939",
            "28th August 1939",
            "3rd September 1939"
          ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In which year, America joined the Second World War?",
            "answer" : "1941",
            "options": [
              "1939",
              "1940",
              "1941",
              "1942"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "When was ancient Rome founded?",
            "answer" : "753 BC",
            "options": [
              "776 BC",
              "753 BC",
              "778 BC",
              "746 BC"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "When was NATO signed?",
            "answer" : "1949",
            "options": [
              "1949",
              "1990",
              "1948",
              "1950"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "In which year, Alexander the Great become the king of Macedonia?",
            "answer" : "336 BC",
            "options": [
              "328 BC",
              "326 BC",
              "336 BC",
              "338 BC"
            ]
          }
      ]
    }
    ,{
      "quizOptions" : [
        {
          "question": "During the First World War, which country signed the Peace Treaty (1917) with Germany?",
          "answer" : "Russia",
          "options": [
            "England",
            "USA",
            "Russia",
            "Austria"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "When did United Kingdom declared war on Germany which lead to World War II?",
          "answer" : "3rd September 1939",
          "options": [
            "4th April 1939",
            "18th August 1939",
            "28th August 1939",
            "3rd September 1939"
          ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In which year, America joined the Second World War?",
            "answer" : "1941",
            "options": [
              "1939",
              "1940",
              "1941",
              "1942"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "When was ancient Rome founded?",
            "answer" : "753 BC",
            "options": [
              "776 BC",
              "753 BC",
              "778 BC",
              "746 BC"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "When was NATO signed?",
            "answer" : "1949",
            "options": [
              "1949",
              "1990",
              "1948",
              "1950"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "In which year, Alexander the Great become the king of Macedonia?",
            "answer" : "336 BC",
            "options": [
              "328 BC",
              "326 BC",
              "336 BC",
              "338 BC"
            ]
          }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
